Stolen Life is a drama film directed by Paul Czinner.
Adapted from the best-selling novel by K.
Benes, A Stolen Life serves as a tour de force for German actress
Elizabeth Bergner, whose husband Paul Czinner directed the film.
Bergner stars as identical twins Sylvina and Martina, whose mild sibling rivalry intensifies when one of the girls
tricks the other's sweetheart Alan McKenzie (Michael Redgrave) into proposing to the wrong twin.
Sylvina Lawrence / Martina Lawrence, played by Elisabeth Bergner.
Alan MacKenzie, played by Michael Redgrave.
Thomas E. Lawrence, played by Wilfrid Lawson.
Aunt Helen, played by Mabel Terry-Lewis.
Morgan, played by Richard Ainley.
Garrett, played by Kenneth Buckley.
Stolen Life is a 1939 British drama film directed by Paul Czinner and
starring Michael Redgrave, Elisabeth Bergner and Wilfrid Lawson.
The tone is emotional.